Finding Aid for Band (University of Michigan) records, 1892, 1929-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scrapbooks
  - [Vol. 37], 1975-1976 (Volume 37)
  - [Vol. 38], 1977 (Volume 38)
Related Material
Researchers interested in the University of Michigan Band may also be interested in the following collections and record groups held by the Bentley Historical Library: William D. Revelli papers, James Frederick Lawton papers, School of Music (University of Michigan) records, and University Musical Society records.